[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the long term memory of the computer?", "correct_answer": "Hard Drive", "incorrect_answers": ["Networking Cards", "RAM", "Motherboards"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The semi-autobiographical short stories which A Christmas Story was based on were originally published in what magazine in 1964-1966?", "correct_answer": "Playboy", "incorrect_answers": ["Saturday Evening Post", "Hustler", "Life"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This quote is from what 1978 cult favorite? \nFat, drunk and stupid is no way to go through life son.", "correct_answer": "Animal House", "incorrect_answers": ["Revenge of the Nerds", "American Graffiti", "Porkys"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You shouldnt wash berries before you store them.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the 2 main languages spoken in Madagascar?", "correct_answer": "French and Malagasy", "incorrect_answers": ["Italian and French", "French and English", "English and Malagasy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Cochise in Broken Arrow?", "correct_answer": "Jeff Chandler", "incorrect_answers": ["Kirk Douglas", "Lon Chaney, Jr.", "Jimmy Stewart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which dictator appeared towards the end of the film Blazing Saddles?", "correct_answer": "Adolph Hitler", "incorrect_answers": ["Benito Mussolini", "Francesco Franco", "Nicolae Ceausescu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the big green board in the computer called?", "correct_answer": "motherboard", "incorrect_answers": ["daughter card", "father card", "son board"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Find the correct statement about Stella Adler.", "correct_answer": "She was born in NYC and died in 1997 in NYC.", "incorrect_answers": ["She was born in Russia and died in 2001 in Los Angeles.", "She was born in London and died in 1997 in Evanston, Illinois.", "She was born in Gottingen, Germany and died in 2001 in Chicago."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to an electron that has absorbed a certain amount of energy which is though less than the energy necessary to remove it from the atom?", "correct_answer": "Goes into excited state", "incorrect_answers": ["Nothing", "Decays", "Explodes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do these five countries have in common: Nicaragua, the Philippines, Bolivia, Liechtenstein, Saudi Arabia?", "correct_answer": "They are all named after historic personalities", "incorrect_answers": ["They are all located at an altitude above 1400 km.", "They are the only producers of zirconium", "They all use the US dollar as their unit of currency"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is an arithmetic progression?", "correct_answer": "2, 4, 6, 8...", "incorrect_answers": ["1, 1, 2, 3, 5...", "2, 4, 8, 16...", "1, 2, 3, 5, 7, 11..."]}]